[{"answer": "No no. That's not what I was trying to do", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Calzone.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I got your calzones Mr. my friend. my friend. I am starving my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Hey, if your not doing anything Saturday do you want to meet somewhere ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Calzone.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Why can't two people go and do something without it being a date", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "See what is that? Is that a date", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Calzone.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "All right. I am sorry it's not a date", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Come on up", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Calzone.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I got some Cubans for my friend's wedding. They were more than I wanted to pay for but what the hell", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "I got some Cubans for my friend's wedding. They were more than I wanted to pay for but what the hell", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Calzone.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "that place! I paid", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well this is bad. I am really in a bad situation now", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Calzone.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "What's he going to do? That's exactly the point. Nobody knows what this guy is capable of! He fires people like it is a bodily function", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Gack. Party of four", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Calzone.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Mom! Dad! This is my friend", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "There nice people. I thought you would like them", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Calzone.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Why is this a date", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Come on my friend. Admit it, this is a date", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Calzone.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Saturday night with your parents. Unless I'm your sister this is a date", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Hello. What 's this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Calzone.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Work? It's raining", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Sooooo", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Calzone.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "You don't work in the rain? Your a mailman.", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I did", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Calzone.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Well what could I do? Unless you pay him a visit", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Oh yeah right it's raining", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Calzone.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What time do you need it at", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Can you do it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Calzone.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What kind of a name is my friend anyway", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Calzone.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Where are you going", "qsentId": 30}]